bugguide.net 2005-04-14

# Privacy Policy - BugGuide.Net

Home » About

I take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about this web site's privacy policy.

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

This policy covers how I treat personal information that this web site collects and receives. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name or e-mail address that is not otherwise publicly available.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

I may update this policy. I will notify you about significant changes to this policy by sending an email to the system email address specified in your account or by placing a notice on this web site.

**Information Collection and Use**

This web site collects personal information when you register and when you visit this web site. When you register this web site asks for information such as your name and email address. Once you register with this web site and sign in, you are not anonymous. This web site automatically receives and records information, including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you request, from your browser and records it in server logs.

**Viewing and Updating Your Information**

You can always access the personal information you have provided to this web site by clicking on "Your Account", a hyperlink in the upper right corner of the pages of this web site. You can make changes to this information to update your account anytime.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

I do not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or companies except when I have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

As a response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise my legal rights or defend against legal claims;

I believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of this web site's Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law.

**Cookies**

In order to provide you with ease of access to your account, this web site will place a cookie (a small text file) on any computer from which you log-in to this web site and check "Remember me". When you revisit this web site, this cookie will enable the web site to recognize you without requiring you to retype any password or other user identification.

Temporary cookies may also be used to remember your preferences during your visit, even if you do not have an account.

**Contacting You**

I reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to this web site, such as administrative messages, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.
